Roy Justus Papers
Roy Justus Papers
- Artwork
  - By Justus
    - 1954 Jul-Dec, 137 items (Oversize 15)
      Nov 13: Shooting in the senate chamber
      Nov 16: No caption
      Nov 17: Change of tactics
      Nov 18: Even if they have to fight for it
      Nov 19: Did someone say peaceful co-existence?
      Nov 20: Most anytime now
      Nov 22: Politics makes strange bed-fellows
      Nov 23: High and dry
      Nov 24: And a strong arm
      Nov 25: Still much to be thankful for
      Nov 26: Out of the cloud
      Nov 27: That new style is here again
      Nov 29: I'm getting tired of hash!
      Nov 30: Another question of co-existence
      Dec 1: Frightening the enemy
      Dec 2: New caddy?
      Dec 3: Now that looks better!
      Dec 4: Santa's toughest job
      Dec 6: Another bi-partisan effort
      Dec 7: One campaign ends - another begins
      Dec 8: An empty stomach makes a poor student
      Dec 9: Revised slogan
      Dec 10: Branding his elephant
      Dec 11: Dad can dream, too!
      Dec 13: As a last resort
      Dec 14: Beginning to follow everywhere
      Dec 15: Rolling out the carpet
      Dec 16: Wonder what's inside
      Dec 17: Is it just the Christmas spirit?
      Dec 18: Unbalanced but stable
      Dec 20: The moths and the flame
      Dec 21: Still on the loose
      Dec 22: No hibernation for this bear
      Dec 23: As the new semester begins
      Dec 24: The most wanted gift of all
      Dec 25: Eternal hope
      Dec 27: He'll be along directly
      Dec 28: Calendar reformers
      Dec 29: Hammer and sickle
      Dec 30: The legislative tight-wire
    - 1955 Jan-Jun, 145 items (Oversize 16)
      Jan 1: He must be new around here
      Jan 3: Reception committee
      Jan 3: One's afraid he will - one's afraid he won't
      Jan 4: After sixteen years of prospecting
      Jan 5: Uncle's watch dog
      Jan 6: Painting with broad strokes
      Jan 7: Our bulwark
      Jan 8: Stout fellow
      Jan 10: Hitch-hiking isn't enough
      Jan 11: Where do you think you are going?
      Jan 12: Our very own coexistence policy
      Jan 13: And some more teachers
      Jan 14: Just a matter of getting used to it
      Jan 15: The balance in nature
      Jan 17: Two related news items
      Jan 18: The high cost of survival
      Jan 19: Well, hello, there!
      Jan 20: The double life of Chiang Kai-Shek
      Jan 21: That demon, temptation, again!
      Jan 22: Can't afford to flunk this course
      Jan 24: The hot potato
      Jan 25: Are there two Chinas or one?
      Jan 26: Trying to keep it on ice
      Jan 27: Iron curtain co-existence
      Jan 28: Just having a look
      Jan 29: Before it gets out of control
      Jan 30: Where economic doctors disagree
      Jan 31: One of our greatest weapons
      Feb 1: Cease fire!
      Feb 2: Waiting for a more favorable moment
      Feb 3: Are the skies clearing?
      Feb 4: Back to normalcy in Russia
      Feb 7: The Pekingese and the porcupine
      Feb 8: A lady in distress
      Feb 9: Moscow weather flags again
      Feb 10: The bear of many faces
      Feb 11: The AFL-CIO merger
      Feb 12: With malice toward none...
      Feb 13: This is the kind of shooting I favor
      Feb 14: A helping hand
      Feb 15: Not music to his ears!
      Feb 16: The simplified form
      Feb 17: The big parade
      Feb 18: What is our Formosa policy?
      Feb 19: Chicago, San Francisco - who cares?
      Feb 21: Still lots of smoke
      Feb 22: Calling on miss voter
      Feb 23: Let me go - let me go -!
      Feb 24: What a place for speech making
      Feb 25: Weather outlook: thaw
      Feb 26: The big kick-off
      Mar 2: More bumps ahead
      Mar 4: Mary's little lamb
      Mar 5: Better get going, woodchopper!
      Mar 7: He even frightens himself
      Mar 8: A - blasts
      Mar 9: Fishing' just hasn't been good lately!
      Mar 10: Still down the middle of the road
      Mar 11: Look - two hands!
      Mar 12: Speaking frankly
      Mar 14: When U.S.A. and U.S.S.R. farmers meet
      Mar 15: The rasslin' match
      Mar 16: Frank talk from the doctor
      Mar 17: Mighty voice of authority
      Mar 18: Rival editors
      Mar 19: Just one more hurdle
      Mar 21: Woes of the librarian
      Mar 23: How damaging is the fall out?
      Mar 24: Washington melodrama
      Mar 26: Sure that isn't another mirage?
      Mar 28: The finish line
      Mar 29: Probably be around for quite a spell
      Mar 30: In the middle
      Mar 31: Whistling in the dark
      Apr 1: The thirty day reprieve
      Apr 2: Chiang's drifting island
      Apr 4: A lot of fiddling
      Apr 6: Returning the tribute
      Apr 7: Timber!
      Apr 8: Little red riding hood modernized
      Apr 9: Easy wisdom
      Apr 11: The big four
      Apr 13: The goose and the golden eggs
      Apr 14: Counter influence
      Apr 15: Persistent suitor
      Apr 16: Can you detect any reaction?
      Apr 18: Low tide
      Apr 19: The Bandung conference
      Apr 21: Traveling salesman
      Apr 21: Strong stuff
      Apr 22: Shaky platform
      Apr 23: Lookalikes
      Apr 25: How to-let go with dignity
      Apr 26: And the meek shall inherit the earth
      Apr 27: Two pair
      Apr 28: Still in pursuit
      Apr 29: Letting George do it
      Apr 30: Not a very good training diet
      May 2: The long wind up
      May 6: No caption
      May 7: After the big one
      May 9: Remarkable survival powers
      May 10: The harbingers
      May 11: Real or artificial
      May 12: Arrangements committee
      May 13: How's your garden?
      May 14: When the bear goes up the mountain
      May 16: The great tug of war
      May 17: Something to keep in mind
      May 18: Red bloc's security set up
      May 19: Good or bad - it's relaxing!
      May 20: Market investigator
      May 20: Another drought seems broken
      May 21: No shift in this position
      May 23: Agonizing reappraisal
      May 24: That feeling is growing stronger
      May 25: Coming or going
      May 26: Experience has made him cautious
      May 27: The new regime
      May 30: Another memorial day
      Jun 1: Bargaining
      Jun 2: His ideal neutral corridor
      Jun 4: As the Russians depart
      Jun 6: At the summit
      Jun 7: Modern jolly roger
      Jun 8: Platform unchanged
      Jun 9: Now, what?
      Jun 10: Better than troop movements
      Jun 11: The big issue
      Jun 14: Diplomatic tightrope
      Jun 15: Man-size job
      Jun 16: Hitting the ties
      Jun 17: 84th congress fireworks
      Jun 18: Tourist in America
      Jun 20: Brighter year by year
      Jun 21: Retreat from Moscow and Peiping
      Jun 22: Mind if I look over your shoulder?
      Jun 23: And no fair peeking!
      Jun 24: Not too attractive a June bride
      Jun 25: Already at the summit
      Jun 27: Just a non-partisan observation
      Jun 28: Diagnosing the new smile
      Jun 29: How to let go simultaneously
      Jun 30: Davy Crockett a fisherman, too?
    - 1955 Jul-Dec, 134 items (Oversize 17)
      Jul 1: Somebody isn't tuned in
      Jul 4: July 4, 1955
      Jul 5: Speech spoiler
      Jul 6: Sinking hose in Washington, too?
      Jul 7: There goes another theory
      Jul 8: High on the summit
      Jul 10: The beginning of some understanding?
      Jul 11: Boom and bust
      Jul 12: Another summit
      Jul 13: To the rescue
      Jul 14: What a mascot!
      Jul 15: The strain is beginning to show
      Jul 17: The diggers
      Jul 18: When farmers get together
      Jul 19: Beginning to pile up
      Jul 20: It'll take a lot of pumping
      Jul 21: On the agenda sooner or later
      Jul 22: A test of sincerity at the summit
      Jul 23: A man about to take a vacation
      Jul 25: The harvest
      Jul 26: Mary's little lamb
      Jul 27: Difficulties of the descent
      Jul 28: Donkey searching for an issue
      Jul 29: Double or nothing
      Jul 30: Beating swords into plowshares
      Aug 1: The bridge isn't strong enough for that
      Aug 2: A couple of other summits
      Aug 3: Clean as a hound's tooth!
      Aug 4: January forecast: cold and snow
      Aug 5: Voice from the dark
      Aug 6: Ivan, this is my best tool!
      Aug 8: Business isn't booming for everybody
      Aug 9: The big shot
      Aug 10: Speaking of satellites!
      Aug 11: Gristmill
      Aug 12: Hurricane Ike
      Aug 13: Grinnin' him down?
      Aug 15: If at first you don't succeed...
      Aug 16: As the stork flies
      Aug 17: Fisherman's luck
      Aug 18: Selecting his '56th campaign button
      Aug 19: Uncle Samson and Delilah?
      Aug 20: Smoke nuisance
      Aug 22: The by-product
      Aug 23: What are your intentions?
      Aug 24: Kitten and ball of yarn
      Aug 25: Another summit
      Aug 26: Step right up, folks!
      Aug 27: Love me, love my dog
      Aug 29: They're off!
      Aug 30: Cure worse than the disease
      Aug 31: To spike the big gun
      Sep 2: Era of good feeling
      Sep 3: Handicap race
      Sep 5: Industrial show of his own
      Sep 6: Liberty bell
      Sep 7: Still in the debate stage
      Sep 8: The land of milk and honey
      Sep 9: Oh, yeah?
      Sep 10: The haunted house
      Sep 12: Speaking of over-production
      Oct 4: Freedom's bulwark still stands
      Oct 5: Change in the '56 prospects
      Oct 6: Between smiles
      Oct 7: Going to be quite a stew!
      Oct 8: The woes of agriculture
      Oct 10: That red feather lift
      Oct 11: School daze
      Oct 12: He's gotta hurry!
      Oct 13: Change in the cold war
      Oct 14: Monkey business
      Oct 15: Easy for the sidewalk superintendent
      Oct 17: Another booming business
      Oct 18: End of the trail
      Oct 19: Warming up for a short '56 race
      Oct 20: And now the valley
      Oct 21: Look who has the ball
      Oct 22: Adlai: but this is not easy!
      Oct 24: My, how Halloween has changed!
      Oct 25: The cheering isn't too spirited yet
      Oct 26: Jubilant farm animals
      Oct 27: The corner stone
      Oct 28: Political nightmare
      Oct 29: Over-production here, too!
      Oct 31: Study in expressions
      Nov 1: I don't smell any smoke!
      Nov 2: The thinker
      Nov 3: I've seen him before!
      Nov 4: Free ball
      Nov 5: Here we go again!
      Nov 7: Profile shot
      Nov 8: Another balloon barrage
      Nov 9: In the waiting room
      Nov 10: Dangerous juggling
      Nov 11: Just as we're ready for a swim
      Nov 12: Political duck hunters
      Nov 14: Why does a bear act like a bear
      Nov 15: Ladies and gentlemen
      Nov 16: They're off!
      Nov 17: Prelude to 1956
      Nov 18: The Greeks called him atlas
      Nov 19: For all the world to see
      Nov 21: Feudin' ground
      Nov 23: The early bird
      Nov 24: His idea of a thanksgiving turkey
      Nov 25: Road block
      Nov 26: I see they are signaling again
      Nov 28: It's an ill wind
      Nov 29: The fall-out will be terrific
      Nov 30: Not a bit too soon!
      Dec 1: Help!
      Dec 2: The old story of the ins and the outs
      Dec 3: Kremlin body-guard
      Dec 5: Christmas gift
      Dec 6: Fancy meeting you here!
      Dec 7: Against a somber background
      Dec 8: Diplomacy race
      Dec 9: Phew!
      Dec 10: Some farmers just aren't reasonable
      Dec 13: Scrooge
      Dec 15: His pen is mightier than the sword
      Dec 16: Strong head winds
      Dec 17: The spirit of Moscow
      Dec 19: How big the bag?
      Dec 21: Scorekeeper
      Dec 22: Slogans or clubs?
      Dec 23: Progress - Kremlin style
      Dec 24: Unconquerable spirit
      Dec 26: May I exchange these for just anything?
      Dec 27: The weather is never more than half bad
      Dec 28: Strange perch for a dove
      Dec 28: Trying to return a package (GOP elephant shoving package of John Birch Society into adjustments window)
      Dec 29: Huffing and puffing
      Dec 31: This is no bedtime story, kid!
    - 1956 Jan-Jun, 148 items (Oversize 18)
      Jan 2: Who killed Cock Robin?
      Jan 4: There's that question again
      Jan 5: Getting ready for the parade
      Jan 6: Looks rosy
      Jan 7: Another installment due
      Jan 9: Peace and prosperity
      Jan 10: The big issue
      Jan 11: Hog-calling contest
      Jan 12: Hold onto your hat, Madame!
      Jan 13: Poor fellow!
      Jan 14: Suspense
      Jan 16: The hero
      Jan 17: Shucks!
      Jan 18: Election fireworks
      Jan 19: Great day for the comrades
      Jan 20: Getting sort of crowded
      Jan 21: The only cloud in sight
      Jan 23: Look who fell in!
      Jan 24: The long ride
      Jan 25: Hey!
      Jan 26: Plenty of grist for the mill
      Jan 27: There's that smile again
      Jan 28: His hat's in!
      Jan 30: Handicap race
      Jan 31: Hey - how about cutting some wood?
      Feb 1: Confused picture in the form debate
      Feb 2: Who's betting on the rabbit?
      Feb 3: Better than smoking guns
      Feb 4: The honey tree
      Feb 5: Nothing but brotherly love
      Feb 7: Will Ike run?
      Feb 8: Test of endurance continued
      Feb 9: Green thumb test
      Feb 10: The vanguard
      Feb 11: Top man on the totem pole
      Feb 13: The new star
      Feb 14: Bubble gum
      Feb 15: Ambulance chaser
      Feb 16: It never rains but it pours
      Feb 17: Throwing down the gauntlet
      Feb 18: Veto
      Feb 20: Hot potato surplus
      Feb 21: At the brink
      Feb 22: Khrushchev: no one-man rule in Russia
      Feb 23: Something he didn't ask for!
      Feb 24: Too many cooks
      Feb 25: Ike, that's not quail
      Feb 27: Harvest time
      Feb 28: Much of it will be done with mirrors
      Feb 29: Those hats make good targets
      Mar 1: Looks like a hole-in-one!
      Mar 2: Campaign sound wagon
      Mar 3: The prize grows less attractive
      Mar 4: The middleman
      Mar 5: Who says the office is neglected?
      Mar 6: Another brink
      Mar 7: Every four years - the William Tell act
      Mar 8: Contest without a winner
      Mar 9: His whipping boy
      Mar 10: Rigid
      Mar 11: Olympics shot-put
      Mar 12: The snake charmer
      Mar 13: Sincere smile
      Mar 14: Difficulty in keeping a cool head
      Mar 15: Another coonskin cap
      Mar 16: A cloud no bigger than a man's head
      Mar 17: Has his over confidence back again
      Mar 18: Minnesota primary feature
      Mar 19: Banishment of a villain
      Mar 20: The battle line
      Mar 21: The stampede
      Mar 22: Ringmaster extraordinary
      Mar 23: The meaning of the primaries
      Mar 24: The fall-out
      Mar 25: Contest between the girls now
      Mar 26: More pressure - and hurry!
      Mar 27: Broken idol - broken heart!
      Mar 28: The creeper
      Mar 29: Just as elusive as ever
      Mar 30: Lengthening shadow
      Mar 31: Important wheel, too!
      Apr 1: No, no, Ivan - not that one!
      Apr 2: What will the harvest be?
      Apr 3: Post-mortem afterthoughts
      Apr 4: What a team! (farm bill, campaign politics)
      Apr 5: One type of farming that pays off
      Apr 6: Chinese laundry
      Apr 7: I smell something burning!
      Apr 8: The tax payer needs more time
      Apr 9: The idol speaks
      Apr 10: Safer than fighting the champ
      Apr 11: What's cookin'?
      Apr 12: Nice recovery
      Apr 13: Much noise - little meal
      Apr 14: Spoiling a picnic
      Apr 15: And a shortage of good ball players
      Apr 16: This is how to do it, boys!
      Apr 17: Invasion of that tight little isle
      Apr 18: Who put pussy in the well?
      Apr 19: The weapons are chosen
      Apr 20: What's he so smug about?
      Apr 23: Political hat styling
      Apr 24: Talk about a third party
      Apr 25: Medicine man
      Apr 26: A war of nerves at home
      Apr 27: Springtime
      Apr 28: The target moves in closer
      Apr 30: Injuns!
      May 1: The new peaceful co-existence
      May 2: Convention noise makers
      May 3: That smile's getting sort of spooky
      May 4: International beach combers
      May 5: Watching the melon grow
      May 7: One surplus after another
      May 8: What's in your bag?
      May 9: Walls of Jericho?
      May 10: Hoosier calm
      May 11: Uncle's splitting headache
      May 12: Justifiable skepticism
      May 14: Come, gentle spring
      May 15: Gosh!-do you suppose...?
      May 16: Still in the army
      May 17: Out of the wild blue yonder
      May 18: The big bank
      May 19: Old mother Hubbard
      May 21: Spring flood
      May 22: Most any time now
      May 23: Boy - what fire power!
      May 24: Forbidden fruit
      May 25: Guided missile jitters
      May 26: The leaning tower of Asia
      May 28: Why not a visit to the U.S.- during political campaign
      May 29: Political campaign hybrid
      May 30: Spiking it?
      May 31: Usual after-dinner snooze
      Jun 1: Now is the time for...
      Jun 2: Test of courage
      Jun 4: All the world is a stage
      Jun 5: Not the way to ride coattails!
      Jun 6: Graduation and commencement
      Jun 7: Inseparable
      Jun 8: The unexpected drought
      Jun 9: Ready volunteers
      Jun 11: Shifting sands of world politics
      Jun 26: New chief of staff
      Jun 27: Smiling skywriter
      Jun 29: How strong the rope
      Jun 30: Strain on the god of war
    - 1956 Jul-Dec, 142 items (Oversize 19)
      Jul 2: Newest display of inventive genius
      Jul 3: Which will be the earlier bird
      Jul 4: The silly season is here again
      Jul 5: One thing is clear
      Jul 6: The A-bomb fall-out
      Jul 7: Untouched by the flames
      Jul 9: Lynching party
      Jul 10: Nixon lectures on neutralism
      Jul 11: Thanks, doc!
      Jul 13: Your speech isn't very convincing!
      Jul 14: There it is again!
      Jul 15: Hardly a Russian invention!
      Jul 16: Campaign handbook
      Jul 17: And everywhere that mary went...
      Jul 18: Concluding the great debate
      Jul 19: International romancing
      Jul 20: Advice from the front man
      Jul 21: The bear comes over the mountain
      Jul 22: Superman
      Jul 23: Neutral harry
      Jul 24: Making sure that it is
      Jul 25: The new thriller
      Jul 26: Just in the nick of time
      Jul 27: Still in the mirage stage
      Jul 28: He's not taking it seriously, is he?
      Jul 29: Don't look now, but...
      Jul 30: Appraising the 84th congress
      Jul 31: Fishin' has never been so good!
      Aug 1: Stassen takes leave of absence
      Aug 3: King Canute sweeping back the waves
      Aug 4: Now, hear this!
      Aug 6: Busy season for the doctors
      Aug 7: Eve, you're a mighty poor marksman!
      Aug 8: The enquiring reporter
      Aug 9: The democrats brink
      Aug 10: Testing his credulity
      Aug 11: Preoccupied
      Aug 13: The '56 conventions kick-off
      Aug 14: Chef's special
      Aug 15: But the prize is more attractive
      Aug 16: Democratic convention sketches
      Aug 18: All dressed up for the big campaign
      Aug 20: Don't believe a word he said!
      Aug 21: The San Francisco Open
      Aug 22: Good grief, it is the driver
      Aug 23: Hardly inspire over confidence
      Aug 24: Bringing the health issue up to date
      Aug 25: 1956 campaign button
      Aug 27: Look out - here comes another one!
      Aug 28: Back to normalcy
      Aug 29: The Volga boatman gets around
      Aug 30: Will it be a shouting contest
      Aug 31: No caption
      Sep 1: School days
      Sep 3: Anvil chorus
      Sep 4: One-way traffic
      Sep 5: New button
      Sep 6: You can always depend on Harry
      Sep 7: Political versions of the farm belt
      Sep 10: World's most crucial race
      Sep 11: Strange bedfellows
      Sep 12: As Maine goes...
      Sep 13: No longer on Ike's team
      Sep 14: He never had it so good
      Sep 15: Feeding the elephant again
      Sep 17: New pilot
      Sep 18: How did he get up there?
      Sep 20: Baby sitter
      Sep 21: Another truth squad
      Sep 22: The chef never misses a thing
      Sep 25: The cat and the canary
      Sep 26: The serenade
      Sep 27: Jack and Jill went up the hill...
      Sep 28: Bringing up the big one
      Sep 29: Vapor trail
      Oct 1: Trailer trouble
      Oct 2: The promised land
      Oct 3: Pretty strong stuff
      Oct 4: Tough target
      Oct 5: This is progress
      Oct 6: Time out!
      Oct 8: Quick - somebody call a truth squad
      Oct 9: It ain't hay!
      Oct 10: Who's getting the Suez tolls?
      Oct 11: Is that something or just a snag?
      Oct 12: The high level debate
      Oct 13: Losing his grip
      Oct 15: The feeler
      Oct 16: Don't get any false notions, mister!
      Oct 17: The health issue
      Oct 18: It's in the bag!
      Oct 19: The market looks bullish!
      Oct 20: How much fall out?
      Oct 22: Ugh!
      Oct 23: Such ingratitude
      Oct 24: The pen fits the hand perfectly
      Oct 25: Pleasing competition
      Oct 26: Idol smashing
      Oct 27: Nuclear contamination
      Oct 29: At last the big issue
      Oct 30: Unwelcome interruption
      Oct 31: Fireworks have been added
      Nov 1: Forecasting the elections
      Nov 2: Both: I smell smoke!
      Nov 3: The pass
      Nov 5: Picking up the pieces
      Nov 6: No caption
      Nov 7: The next job will require teamwork
      Nov 8: The winner!
      Nov 10: Woman's work is never done!
      Nov 12: Quadrennial left-overs
      Nov 14: The captive
      Nov 17: Bear hug
      Nov 19: The twain have met
      Nov 20: Fire!
      Nov 21: Defense strategists
      Nov 22: Trying to keep corks under water
      Nov 23: Disturbing the peace
      Nov 24: Delivering the new chinaware
      Nov 26: Humpty dumpty's convalescence
      Nov 28: The usual aftermath
      Nov 29: Middle east Olympics
      Nov 30: Dictator
      Dec 1: No caption
      Dec 3: They come up with every shower
      Dec 7: Veteran ambassador of good will
      Dec 8: May be he can't read
      Dec 10: A couple of splitting headaches
      Dec 12: Hot foot
      Dec 14: It's a cold war
      Dec 15: New light on the subject
      Dec 17: Two bags full
      Dec 18: Somebody's ears burning
      Dec 19: A cold war thaw
      Dec 20: Which way is the wind blowing?
      Dec 22: Interrupted journey
      Dec 24: Who will lend a hand?
      Dec 24: Party harmony
      Dec 26: Titoitis
      Dec 27: He thinks he's got problems!
      Dec 28: It won't come off!
      Dec 29: Anyway, he's getting his feet wet
    - 1957 Jan-Jun, 147 items (Oversize 20)
      Jan 1: Ride 'im, cowboy
      Jan 2: Crystal ball
      Jan 3: Afterthought
      Jan 4: Hitching-up time
      Jan 5: Hardly inspires a superiority complex
      Jan 7: The most troublesome aggression
      Jan 8: Close scrutiny
      Jan 9: Forecast: continued cold
      Jan 10: State of the union
      Jan 11: Heavy portfolio
      Jan 12: In the waiting room
      Jan 14: New thriller
      Jan 15: The big club
      Jan 16: Drought
      Jan 17: No caption
      Jan 18: Is he stealing the show?
      Jan 19: Fiddling
      Jan 21: Gosh!
      Jan 22: Still under the gun
      Jan 23: Natural aversion for high places
      Jan 24: Strong man
      Jan 25: Flying-saucers over the mid-east
      Jan 26: Reviving a myth
      Jan 28: Inflation here, too!
      Jan 29: What a target
      Jan 30: Tis indeed a trouble-spot!
      Jan 31: Lost-one good rickshaw boy
      Feb 2: Here comes another hot potato
      Feb 4: Tying uncle's hands
      Feb 5: Up in a cloud
      Feb 6: The cleaners
      Feb 7: Same old slippery stuff
      Feb 8: New garden venture
      Feb 9: Nice kitty!
      Feb 11: Persistent Polly
      Feb 12: Is this the supreme test?
      Feb 13: Road map trouble
      Feb 14: Wait 'til he catches his breath
      Feb 15: International courting
      Feb 16: Is this a sample of Kremlin humor?
      Feb 18: Chronic vitamin deficiency